<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Books><Book id="1"><title>Dance students spring to center stage for final show</title><author>Tasha Sandoval</author><summary>For four nights in a row, the department of theater and dance will artistically invade Pickard, providing the Bowdoin community with a variety of student dance pieces for their final spring show.</summary></Book><Book id="2"><title>Bowdoin Chorus features Haydn, Williams in year-end concert</title><author>Quinn Cohane</author><summary>The Bowdoin Chorus will bring its year to a harmonious end with a final concert this weekend. Accompanied by a chamber orchestra, the 60-person ensemble made up of Bowdoin students, staff and Midcoast community members will be singing two pieces: Franz Joseph Haydn's "Insanae et vanae curae" and Ralph Vaughan Williams' "Dona nobis pacem."</summary></Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="3"> 
		<title>Galle exhibit grows to new heights in Coleman Burke</title> 
		<author>Hannah Hoyt</author> 
		<summary>Just down Main Street, a small pine forest is suspended several feet above the ground: over 50 trees hang from the ceiling of Coleman Burke Gallery in Fort Andross as part of Jacob Galle's recent installation.</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="4"> 
		<title>City Scene: Finding meat-free, taste-full food</title> 
		<author>Rachel Goldman</author> 
		<summary> 
			Each week the Orient spotlights different aspects of the arts and entertainment scene in Portland. This week's installment focuses on venues for vegetarian food.
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="5"> 
		<title>Students to read English department prize pieces</title> 
		<author>Daisy Alioto</author> 
		<summary> 
			Students will have the opportunity to hear original fiction this Monday as English Department Prize victors read their winning compositions aloud. 
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="6"> 
		<title>Sounds of the Middle East to greet Studzinski</title> 
		<author>Daisy Alioto</author> 
		<summary> 
			The Bowdoin Middle Eastern Ensemble will be performing at 8 p.m. in Studzinski Recital Hall on Monday April 26. 
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="7"> 
		<title>Student prints put art and food on display</title> 
		<author>Rachel Goldman</author> 
		<summary> 
			Students may have noticed someting special in Moulton Dining Hall this week: the 12x24 prints lining main dining room's walls.  
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="8"> 
		<title>An Ivies drinking syllabus: The perfect drink for any time of day</title> 
		<author>Eric Adrolino</author> 
		<summary> 
			Ivies Week is a special time for Bowdoin students. We crawl out of the libraries and classrooms and discover an unusually hospitable climate. 
After five months of darkness and permafrost, we can now pretend that our college experience isn't so awful. 
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="9"> 
		<title>Music revolutionizes, future still a mystery</title> 
		<author>Tyler Patton</author> 
		<summary> 
			Over the past two decades, the music industry has undergone a drastic revolution. It's crazy to think about how far it has come in such a short period of time.
 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
			
	<Book id="10"> 
		<title>Ben Lovell '10, Joe Henderson '10 and Kathy Yang '10</title> 
		<author>Rachel Goldman</author> 
		<summary> 
			BEN LOVELL '10, JOE HENDERSON '10 AND KATHY YANG  '10

 
		</summary> 
	</Book> 
	
		
 
</Books>