<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>The Bowdoin Orient</title>
    <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/</link>
    <description>The student newspaper of Bowdoin College, Brunswick, Maine.</description>
    <copyright>Copyright 2004, The Bowdoin Orient. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <category>Newspapers</category> 
    <pubDate>Fri, 7 May 2004 00:00:01 EST</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 7 May 2004 00:00:01 EST</lastBuildDate>
    <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title>Faculty postpones distribution vote</title>
      <description>After a lengthy debate over a proposed amendment, the faculty failed to vote on the new proposed distribution requirements at its meeting Monday. Time only allowed for the approval of a controversial amendment before a sufficient number of faculty members opted to postpone further debate.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=1</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=1</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Merit-based scholarship questioned</title>
      <description>According to Bowdoin's financial aid website, the College has been need-blind for the past ten years. However, Bowdoin has been offering 100 stipends worth $3,000 to accepted students on the basis of "talent" rather than financial need for the last two years.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=2</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=2</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tree unable to sustain Ivies Weekend damage</title>
      <description>Four students have been implicated in an attempt to chop down a tree on the Brunswick Apartments quad Saturday night. A resident reported the incident to Security at 2:00 p.m. Sunday.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=3</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=3</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Congressional campaigns heat up</title>
      <description>Next Wednesday voters will determine whether or not "size matters" when they cast their ballots for the Bowdoin Congressional race. In the meantime, both candidates, Jim Weeks '04 and Lenz Balan '04, are jockeying for position in the final days before the election.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=4</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=4</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Future of diversity addressed at debate</title>
      <description>As the academic year comes to a close, administrators, faculty, staff, and students met for the third collective debate to think about diversity in the College's future. The debate addressed the following questions: How do you imagine diversity in five years? Would you like our sense of difference to change, expand or narrow in any way? Do you envision more people like yourself or truly different from yourself at Bowdoin in the coming years?</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=5</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=5</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admissions announces Class of 2008 demographics</title>
      <description>Over the course of the last month, the Admissions Office has been busy recruiting the Class of 2008. While the composition of the class has not yet been finalized, the College admitted 1,130 applicants from 47 states, the District of Columbia, the Virgin Islands, and 27 other countries.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=6</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=1&#38;id=6</guid> 
      <category>News</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Year In Review: Champs, challenges, and choices</title>
      <description>The following is the Orient's compilation of the most important stories that have appeared in this publication during the last nine months. We feel these are the stories that have had the greatest impact on our college lives since September 2003.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=3&#38;id=1</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=3&#38;id=1</guid> 
      <category>Features</category>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fast Features: Campus Weather</title>
      <description>Today. Partly cloudy. Highs in the upper 60s. West winds around 10 mph. Becoming northwest 15 to 20 mph in the afternoon.</description>
      <link>http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=3&#38;id=2</link> 
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://orient.bowdoin.edu/orient/article.php?date=2004-05-07&#38;section=3&#38;id=2</guid> 
      <category>Features</category>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>